The year is 2048.
现在是2048年
Evolving technologies can no longer be regulated.
高端技术不的发展已超出可控范围
Dangerous advancements forever alter the criminal landscape.
犯罪领域被某些危险性高的技术彻底改变
Police are not prepared.
警方措手不及
Law enforcement combats this corruption with a new line of defense...
执法人员引入了一队新的力量 来应对这严峻问题
but not all are created equal.
但所有成员的情况不尽相同
The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
DRN的构想是尽可能地接近人类
They were based on a program called Synthetic Soul.
他们是基于一个叫人造灵魂的程序
That's one of the crazy ones.
这是...那种疯子
- I'll lead you in? - Let's go.
- 我带你进去? - 走吧
Now all cops- human and manmade together-
现在 警方所有人员 人类和非人类一起
take on the battle to watch over us all.
开始了这场监管我们所有人的战争
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 机器之心 第一季第2集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 机器之心 第一季第2集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：光影
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：柚子熊猫 校对：酒囊饭袋 时间轴：光影
You are incredible.
你真美
Let's get more comfortable, hmm? That okay?
那我们玩点更尽兴的 嗯? 怎么样?
You nervous?
你紧张了?
It seems like you've got a lot on your mind.
你心里好像有很多事
Actually... I do.
是的 的确
What are you doing?
你要做什么?
I've passed all my tests. I'm clean.
我所有检测都通过了 我没问题的
Would you mind?
不介意吧?
This won't hurt.
不疼的
You don't have to do anything if you don't want to.
你要是不愿意 可以什么都不做的
People come to me for all sorts of reasons.
男人出于各种各样的原因来找我
Some want to talk or just to be held.
有人想聊天 有人只想被拥抱
Look, why don't we just have some fun?
我们做点更有趣的嘛
People look for connections in different ways.
每个人都有他独特的相处方法
Someone who cares about them.
是真正在乎他们的人
Andrei!
Andrei!
Look at this.
看呐
Last one.
最后一步了
I promise.
我保证
Get dressed.
穿上衣服
- CSI finished upstairs? - Shouldn't be long, sir.
- CSI(犯罪现场调查组)的人搞完没? - 应该快了 长官
- You're a bot. - Yes, I am.
- 你是机器人 - 对啊 没错
Cool! What can you do?
好酷 你能做什么呢?
- Whoa. - Oh, awesome!
哇哦 好棒!
Are you a robot, too?
你也是机器人吗?
No, I'm human.
不 我是人类
Oh. What can you do?
哦 那你能做什么呢?
Watch this.
看好哦
No, no, no.
哦不 别怕
It doesn't hurt. I got... I got a synthetic leg!
不疼的 我这条腿是人造的!
I haven't even been a child, and I know that would scare one.
我没当过小孩儿都知道那个很吓人
What's the matter with you? You have negative energy, man.
你想什么呢 浑身都是负能量啊 哥们儿
- My energy's great. - Why don't you like kids?
- 我的能量很好啊 - 你为什么不喜欢孩子呢?
I never said I don't like kids. You said I don't like kids.
我从来没这样说过 是你说我不喜欢孩子的
Children can sense electromagnetic fields, John.
孩子能感应到电磁场 John
- That's a bunch of baloney. - They can sense discomfort, frustration and bad energy.
- 扯淡 - 他们还能感受到郁闷 沮丧 还有负能量
As do felines. I bet you have an issue with cats, too, am I right?
跟猫一样 我打赌 你也不喜欢猫 对吧?
Hey. My issue with cats is none of your business.
嘿 我不喜欢猫也不关你的事
- I'm allergic to cats. - Maybe the cats are allergic to you.
- 我对猫过敏 - 没准儿猫对你也过敏
You ever consider that?
你有想过吗?
Victim is ID'd as Sebastian Jones. He paid for the room with cash.
死者名叫Sebastian Jones 用现金订的房
Front desk said he showed up with a woman. Red hair, 20s.
前台说他跟一名女子一起出现的 女子红色头发 20岁左右
About a half hour later, two men showed up.
大概半小时之后 又来了两名男子
There are no fingerprints.
这里根本找不到指纹
I don't think we're gonna get anything from Forensics.
估计法证那边也不会有任何结果的
Everything is tainted in here.
现场整个都被破坏了
They used a DNA bomb.
他们用了DNA破坏弹
I hate that stuff.
最讨厌那种东西了
Absorption round, third gen.
吸声弹 第三代的
Wouldn't have made a sound. These guys are good.
一点声音都不会有 这伙人身手不错
Any surveillance?
有监控吗?
She came in at 6:15 p. m.
她下午6:15进来的
They arrived 20 minutes later.
20分钟之后这俩人又进来
They're wearing FlashMask.
他们脸上都涂了闪光粉
They took his bag.
他们把死者的包拿走了
John.
John
She's an android.
她是机器人
What do we have on our victim?
死者什么情况?
Sebastian Jones was a high-end sex trade bot-maker.
Sebastian Jones 高端性伴侣机器人制造者
Yeah, too bad he's dead.
嗯 可惜竟然死了
Could've made you a girlfriend.
不然还能给你做个女朋友
I'm not the one with the online dating profile.
在网上婚恋交友的又不是我
I don't have an online dating profile.
我才没有网上婚恋交友
You do now.
现在有了
"Capricorn who loves danger. "
"喜欢危险的摩羯"
Okay. While you're at it, why don't you put down
好吧 既然你已经进网站了
- "Recently lost partner in tragic freeway accident. " - Guys, what do we have?
怎么不干脆写上 "近期遭遇高速公路车祸 搭档在车祸中丧生"?
Sebastian Jones' company is called Orillian Sapients.
Sebastian Jones的公司叫Orillian Sapients
- They specialize in advanced sexual robotics. - Is this one of his sexbots?
- 专做高端性伴侣机器人 - 这个会不会是他公司的机器人?
- We don't know. - Sexbots are licensed.
- 还不知道 - 但性伴侣机器人是有牌照的
- Who's it registered to? - It's not registered to anybody.
- 这个登记在谁的名下? - 没有登记在任何人名下
Someone owns it. It has to be registered.
这是属于某个人的 不可能没登记
What else do we know about his life?
那他的个人情况呢?
No spouse, no kids, no criminal record.
没有妻儿 也没有犯罪记录
Legitimate businessman.
是个守法的商人
- Inventor. - He has 23 patents to his name and is credited as a pioneer in developing the artificial blush response.
- 还是发明家 - 名下有23项专利 被称为人工脸色反应研究的先锋
Every red-blooded man in this city owes a debt to this fallen genius.
这座城市没哪个男的不欠这位陨落的天才账的
Why, because he makes sex trade bots?
为什么 因为他是做性伴侣机器人的?
Call 'em "bang bots. " They actually like it.
那叫"啪啪机器人" 可招人喜欢了
And you know this from experience?
这是你的经验之谈么?
- You say it like it's a bad thing. - Crimes in the sex trade are down
- 怎么说得跟啥坏事似的 - 自从这种机器人出现
- 38% since the bots were introduced. - Right? Do that math.
- 性交易领域的犯罪率下降了38% - 好好算算这笔账吧
- The fewer real women that have to sleep with you, Richard, the better off the world is. - Okay.
- 被你睡的人类女子越少 这世界越美好 - 好了
- What else do we know about him? - Sebastian Jones
- 关于他我们还知道些什么? - Sebastian Jones无法清偿债务
Orillian Sapients declared bankruptcy three months ago.
Orillian Sapients公司在三个月前宣布破产了
Creditors seized all of his assets,
所有资产被债主强制抵债
and now they're currently sitting in a repo storage facility.
现正在一间强制收回物品仓库里
(DEFENDANT: JONES, SEBASTIAN) Found a court summons.
有张法院的传票
Sebastian was being sued.
Sebastian被起诉了
- Kennex. - Your case just got weird.
- Kennex - 这案子越来越诡异
I just sent you something. You get it?
我刚给你发了点东西 收到没?
Yeah, I got it.
嗯 收到了
The CSIs went through the elevator at the hotel, scanning spots these guys
CSI的人去酒店电梯进行搜查 检测了那几个人可能触碰过的地方
likely touched, trying to pick up some DNA on them.
希望能提取到一些他们的DNA
Yeah. We didn't find any DNA on the guys, but we found something else.
- 嗯 - 没找到那两个人的DNA 却有了其他发现
That's the first sample they pulled.
那是他们找到的第一份DNA样本
Everywhere she touched, there was DNA from a 25-year-old girl
在她触摸过的地方 总能找到一名25岁女孩的DNA
named Nicole Bloomquist, who was abducted three weeks ago from a parking garage.
女孩叫Nicole Bloomquist 三周前在间停车场被绑架的
Are you telling me the sexbot we're looking for is leaving this girl's DNA?
你是说我们正在追查的这个性伴侣机器人 身上有那个女孩的DNA?
- It seems that way. - How?
- 看起来的确是这样 - 怎么可能呢?
Correct. How?
是啊 怎么可能的?
Ah, there you go. Perfect, perfect.
啊 好啦 可以啦
Oh, look at you. Wriggle monster.
看看你啊 扭来扭去的小家伙
Okay. Mommy'll take it then.
好了 这个妈妈要拿走哦
Give me your hands, give me your face. Beautiful.
擦擦手 擦擦脸 真帅
Another abduction happened. Same M.O. as Nicole Bloomquist.
又一起绑架案 作案方式跟 Nicole Bloomquist被绑时相似
20-something female, parking structure. Cameras were disabled.
被绑架者为20岁左右的女性 案发地点是停车场 监控摄像头被破坏了
There's no surveillance of the abduction.
找不到绑架案发时的录像
And I found three more missing persons cases with the same pattern.
又发生了三宗作案方式相似的绑架案
So, they kill the cams and then take the women.
所以 他们破坏摄像头 然后把目标绑走
Yeah, except this time, something was left behind.
对 除了这次 这次落下些东西
He was in the car. His name is Victor.
他当时在车里 叫Victor
Can I talk to him?
我可以跟他谈谈吗?
- Maybe I should talk to him. He's not good with kids. - Hey.
- 还是我来吧 他不大擅长跟孩子相处 - 嘿
- Or cats. - That-That's not... I'm great with kids, really.
- 还有猫 - 不是这样 我跟孩子处得挺好的 真的
I'm Detective Kennex.
我是Kennex警探
You must be, uh, Victor, right?
你一定是Victor吧?
Victor's a-a good name. It's a good, strong name.
Victor是个好名字 很好 很棒
Look, I know this must be hard...
听我说 我知道对你来说这很难...
but I need you to be brave.
但我需要你勇敢起来 好吗?
Okay? I really need you to tell me what happened with your mom.
我需要你告诉我你妈妈到底怎么了
You like him?
喜欢吗?
I'll give him to you if you want him.
你想要的话 我可以给你
But you got to promise me to look after him
但你得跟我保证 会照顾好他
because he means a lot to me.
因为他对我有很重要的意义
- I promise. - You promise?
- 我保证 - 你保证?
Okay.
那好
I trust you.
我相信你
Look, Victor.
听着 Victor
But I really need your help.
我真的很需要你的帮助
Need you to tell me what happened with your mom.
需要你告诉我妈妈到底发生了什么事
You guys were in a car, right?
你们当时在车里 对吧?
- Your mom got out. - She went to put the trash away.
- 妈妈下车出来了 - 她去扔垃圾
Then what happened?
然后呢 发生了什么?
I saw the car.
我看到有辆车过来
Did you see who was in it?
看到里面有什么人了吗?
Two men.
两个男人
Two men?
两个男人啊?
- What happened then? - The car drove away.
- 然后呢? - 车开走了
What kind of car was it? What color?
那车是什么样的? 什么颜色?
It was a big, silver car.
一辆很大的 银色的车
That's good.
很好
When is my mom coming?
我妈妈什么时候来啊?
Hey, Victor.
嘿 Victor
You did really good.
你做得很好
- What's up? - CSI found the silver sedan on a traffic cam
- 什么事? - CSI在一段交通摄像里发现了那辆银色轿车
a block from the parking structure.
就在距停车场一个街区外的路上
- The license plates tracked back to a red SUV. - They're using stolen plates.
- 根据车牌号追查到一辆红色SUV - 他们用的是偷来的牌照
We got every plate scanner in the city looking for those tags. We'll find that car.
已经利用市里所有车牌扫描仪去找了 一定会找到那辆车的
Okay, two girls were abducted with the same M.O. and one of them,
两名女孩被绑架 作案方式相同 而其中一名女孩
her DNA was found on the sexbot who was with Sebastian Jones when he was murdered.
她的DNA竟然在性伴侣机器人身上被发现 还是Sebastian Jonesher被杀时跟他在一起的机器人
I think we should focus on finding the sexbot that was with Sebastian.
我认为找到跟Sebastian在一起那个机器人是关键
If we can access her memory, we might be able to see what happened in the hotel that night.
如果拿到她的记忆存储 就有可能知道那晚酒店发生的事
And identify who did it.
还有那个行凶的人
- That's our best bet for finding the missing women. - Guys, I might have a new angle.
- 这是找到那些失踪女性最好的办法 - 同志们 有新进展了
I dug into those summonses you found.
我查了你们找到的那张传票
(BOT MAKERS BEGIN LEGAL BATTLE AS FORMER PARTNERS FALL OUT) Sebastian's former business partner Lorenzo Shaw was suing him for intellectual property infringement
是Sebastian之前的合伙人 在起诉他侵犯知识产权
(NEW LINE OF SEXBOTS ANNOUNCED) and he just opened a sexbot showroom downtown for himself- it's motive.
那人自己刚在市区开了一间 性伴侣机器人展示室 这就是动机
- He could be involved. - Check him out.
- 可能跟他有关系 - 去查查
You were surprisingly good with that kid back there, John.
你面对那小男孩时表现得太好了 John
Even though you had to bribe him with a giraffe.
虽然不得不用长颈鹿收买他
Thanks.
谢了
- Do you think his mother is still alive? - I hope so.
- 你觉得他妈妈还活着吗? - 希望吧
Every hour she's gone diminishes the chance of us finding her alive.
她失踪的时间每多一小时 找到她时还活着的几率就少一点
What do you tell a small child when someone dies?
如果有人死的话 你们怎么跟孩子说?
I've never considered that. What you would tell a small child.
我从来没考虑过 要怎么跟小孩说
- Well, you say the same thing that you'd say to an adult. - What do they say?
- 对大人说什么就对孩子说什么 - 那你怎么说?
You tell them that the person that died has gone to a better place.
告诉他们死的人到更好的地方去了
Why would anyone say that when there's no way to really know where living things go when they stop living?
为什么要说这种话呢? 明明没人知道那些活着的死后会去哪
It's designed to give hope and comfort.
这样说是为了给人希望和安慰
To ease the pain.
为了减缓痛苦
People believe it because they need to.
人们会信 因为他们需要这样相信
Hmm, the data I've studied suggests that the best proof of one's existence
据我自己的研究 一个人活过最好的证明
is if one is remembered after they're gone.
就是他死后还有人记得
Was your partner's son told that his father went to a better place?
有人跟你搭档的儿子说过 他父亲去了更好的地方吗?
I don't know.
不知道
You never spoke to your partner's son?
你没跟你搭档的儿子说过话吧
I can understand why that would be hard for you.
我明白为什么你觉得那很难
What did you do with my son?
你们对我儿子做了什么?
Don't worry.
别担心
The authorities will have him by now.
他现在应该在相关机构那里了
- You see, we're... we're not monsters. - I have money!
- 我们又不是怪物 - 我有钱
Anything you want, anything. I'll give you anything.
你们想要什么 我都会给的
Please, I just want to see my son...
求你们 我只想见见我儿子
I already have what I want.
我要的 已经在这了
No, no, no!
不 不要!
Your ex-partner, Sebastian Jones, when was the last time you saw him?
你曾经的合伙人 Sebastian Jones 你最后一次见他是什么时候?
Six months? Seven?
六七个月前吧
- We'd been sort of on the outs lately. - "On the outs"?
- 我们有点小摩擦 - 小摩擦?
You were suing him.
你在起诉他
I have intellectual property rights on designs we developed together at Orillian.
之前在Orillian公司推出的一些设计 我是有知识产权的
What happens to the I.P. rights now that Sebastian's naked?
那现在Sebastian挂了 那些知识产权的所有权发生了什么变化呢?
Um, I mean "dead. " Now that Sebastian's dead.
呃 我的意思是死了 现在Sebastian死了
- What happens to the I.P. rights? - Well, they would naturally revert to me.
- 那些知识产权怎么办呢? - 自然依法转移到我名下
Is this one of your models?
这是你们的产品吗?
No, she's not mine.
不 她不是我做的
What about this one?
那这个呢?
- Or this one? - You ever seen these women before?
- 还有这个? - 你见过这些女人吗?
No, but they're not synthetics.
没有 她们也不是人造的
- How can you be sure? - In my line of work, you get to know.
- 怎么这么肯定? - 你要做这行 就会知道了
You know, I haven't seen one of you in a while.
其实我很久没见你们了
The latest sexbots have a little bit of your old tech in them.
我最新批的机器人还用了点旧技术
They're capable of bonding empathetically with their clients.
她们可以与客户有感情的互动
Sense their moods... and respond accordingly.
能感知他们的情绪 并且做出反应
It's a significant achievement.
这可是重大进展
If your bots are so special, why was Sebastian so in debt?
你们的机器人要真这么特别 Sebastian怎么还会欠那么多债呢?
Well, if you knew Sebastian, you'd understand.
你要认识Sebastian 就会明白了
He was an artist. We were making good money.
他是一个艺术家 我们也赚了不少
But he was determined to create the next line. Better than the last.
但他非要开发比上代更好下一代新产品
He sunk all our capital into new fabs, tooling, subsystems.
把所有资金都投了进去 要研究新的工艺 工具 子系统
He bet the whole company on it.
他把整个公司都赌进去了
And then our biggest client cancelled their contract with us.
然后我们最大的客户却取消了合约
Took us completely by surprise. Bankrupted us.
我们措手不及 只能宣布破产
Who was your biggest client?
谁是你们最大的客户?
Ah, if you don't want to tell me, that's okay. We'll just subpoena your records.
如果你不想告诉我的话 也没关系 只要把记录调出来就行
Shut you down for a few days while we go through them.
不过我们看记录期间你们得关几天门而已
It was an Albanian consortium.
是家阿尔巴尼亚财团
They said they were cutting out the middle man.
他们说要砍掉中间商
You mean they found a new supplier?
你是说他们找到了新的供货商?
Apparently.
显然是
Sebastian couldn't believe that anyone could build a better sexbot than us.
Sebastian不相信能有人做出 比我们的性伴侣机器人更好的产品
The first picture I showed you. Did she belong to the Albanians?
我给你看的第一张照片 她是属于那些阿尔巴尼亚人的吗?
Is she why Sebastian was at the hotel the night he was killed?
因为她 Sebastian才会在那晚 出现在那家酒店又被杀的吗?
I wouldn't know.
- 我不清楚 听我说 我不想再谈论这个话题了 - 他们威胁你了?
No... They were good clients.
不 他们是很好的客户
They always paid on time. And that's all I'm gonna say about them.
付款总是很准时 关于他们 我要说的就这么多
Excuse me. I have customers.
失陪了 我还有客人要招呼
Mr. Shaw?
Shaw先生?
Have you ever heard of people incorporating human DNA into a sexbot?
听没听说过给性伴侣机器人 注入人类DNA这种事?
That's illegal. And I think you know that.
那是违法的 你们应该也知道
You can say you don't like robots all you want.
你完全可以说不喜欢机器人
Your pulse says otherwise.
但你身体的反应却不是那样
What?
什么?
Precisely.
恰恰相反
I want you to hack into Shaw's customer network.
你进入Shaw的客户网
Find the Albanians.
找到那个阿尔巴尼亚财团
- We don't need a warrant? - I agree.
- 不需要搜查令吗? - 我已经同意了
Got it. Five star rating.
找到了 五星评价
What's the plan?
你有什么计划?
Stir the pot.
把水搅浑
They're testing the bots for human DNA.
他们在测那些机器人找人类DNA
Hands out of your pockets.
手拿出来
- You seen this bot? - No.
- 见过这个机器人吗? - 没有
No?
没有吗?
- Seen that bot? - No, no...
- 见过这个机器人没? - 没
We tested all the bots.
所有机器人都检查过了
They all check out. They're clean.
都通过检查了 没问题
- Okay, thanks. - Yup.
- 好 谢啦 - 嗯
Officers.
警官
I'm the manager.
我是这的经理
Can I help you?
有什么可以帮忙的吗?
- Is this one of your bots? - No.
- 这是你们的机器人吗? - 不是
(ELEVATED HEART RATE DETECTED) We got a great selection here. We can get you pretty close to this one.
我们这什么样的都有 可以给您找个跟这个差不多的
Our bots have passed all the required tests. Special rate for cops.
我们的机器人都是通过检测的 警察还有特别优惠呢
- We love cops. - Yeah.
我们就喜欢警察
- Well, great.
- 我们就喜欢警察 - 是吗 那太好了
If you answer all of my questions, maybe I'll let you get to first base.
你要是回答我所有的问题 我就让你来个法式热吻
You ever buy from Sebastian Jones and Lorenzo Shaw?
你们从Sebastian Jones 跟Lorenzo Shaw那买过机器人吗?
- We used to. Not anymore. - Why'd you stop?
- 以前买 现在不了 - 为什么不买了呢?
- We make our own now. - And you're sure that's not one of them?
- 我们现在有自己的产品 - 那你确定这不是你们的机器人?
Already said.
刚已经说过了
John.
John
Detective Stahl needs to talk to us.
Stahl警探有话对我们讲
Thank you, gentlemen.
谢了 先生们
- His vitals suggest that he is lying. - Yup.
- 他的反应表明他在说谎 - 没错
Or he doesn't like you very much.
或者他不怎么喜欢你
Add him to the list of kids and cats.
把他列入小孩儿和猫那一类吧
We got a hit for the silver sedan.
找到那辆银色轿车了
The one that kidnapped Kristen Haseman in the parking garage.
在停车场绑架Kristen Haseman那辆车
We picked it up on a plate scanner.
是在一台牌照扫描仪上发现的
Dorian, watch the sedan as it goes past the scanner.
Dorian 你注意那辆通过扫描仪的车
The license plate changes.
牌照动过手脚
They're using a tag scrambler.
他们用了扰频装置
Once we realized that, we switched to straight surveillance cams and tracked it to an industrial facility off 8th Street.
意识这一点后 我们就直接换了监控摄像 追查到了8号大街一家工厂
What were they doing there?
他们在那做什么?
I don't know, they were there for 20 minutes, and then we lost 'em.
不知道 在那停了20分钟 然后就找不到了
All right, we're three minutes out.
好 我们三分钟后到
What the hell is that?
那是什么?
- Is that Kristen Haseman? - It's not human.
- 是Kristen Haseman吗? - 那不是人类
This is the android from the hotel.
是酒店那个机器人
If this is what they're doing to their sexbots,
如果他们对自己的机器人都这样的话
imagine what they're doing to the women they've abducted.
谁知道会对绑架回来的女人怎样呢
Beautiful green.
好漂亮的绿色
They really have got the color just right.
颜色真的刚刚好
You see, these shots were targeted precisely to shatter the cortical relays
看这几枪 就是这几枪
- and storage centers. - They destroyed her memory.
- 精准地毁坏了皮质继电器和存储中心 - 他们毁掉了她的记忆
Yeah, they wanted to ensure no one could retrieve
对 他们想确保没人能取出
her recorded memories of Sebastian Jones' murder.
她存储的那些关于Sebastian Jones被杀的记忆
- These albinos knew exactly what they were doing. - Albanians.
- 这些阿尔巴纳人很清楚自己要的是什么 - 阿尔巴尼亚人
Well, that, that would make more sense.
哦 那 那样好像更对一些
But there is a small chance that her temporal housing might be intact enough
还有个可能 如果她的颞内存储是完整的
to salvage some of her echoic memory.
就能够取出一些声像记忆
Uh, she might still be able to tell us something about the people that did this.
就是说 她或许能提供些杀手的信息
Apologies, mate. I'm used to being alone when I do this.
抱歉 哥们儿 做这种事时我一般都一个人的
- You might want to look away. - It's fine.
- 你们可以转头看别的 - 没关系的
Why did they peel its skin off?
他们为什么要把皮剥下来呢?
Well, they obviously didn't want us to see that either.
显然那个也不想让我们见到
Wait a minute, the surveillance footage at the hotel.
等等 记得酒店那段监控录像吧
Her hands left traces of human DNA.
她手摸过的地方留下了人类的DNA
You think they're abducting the girls to harvest their skin.
你认为他们绑架女孩子们是为了那些皮肤
If you used human skin, you'd make the best sex machines on the market.
如果用人的皮肤的话 当然能做出市场上最好的机器人
I think Sebastian found out about it.
我觉得Sebastian发现了这点
- That's why they killed him. - Sex machine, bang bot?
- 所以才会被杀 - 性伴侣机器人啊 "啪啪机器人"?
- It's a bit myopic, isn't it? - Not everyone who visits a sexbot is looking for sex.
有点太短视了吧? 又不是所有人找性伴侣机器人都为了性需求
Some people go for the conversation or for a sympathetic ear at the end of a long working day
也有些人只是去说说话 希望工作一整天之后有人能用心倾听
surrounded by people who only ever come to visit when they want something from you.
听他抱怨整天被群有求于他时才来找他的人围着
I'm just saying that, uh,
我只是要说 那个
the neural interface is quite sophisticated.
神经接口相当复杂
Anyway, it appears they're growing skin using DNA from the abducted women.
反正就是他们绑架女人 利用人类DNA种植皮肤
Well, synthetic skin, as good as it is, is a long way from the real thing.
人造的皮肤再怎么好 也比不上真正的人类皮肤
There are pheromones and other biological features that trigger attraction.
那上面有信息素 还有其他生物特性 会产生吸引力的
Here it is.
找到了
Sorry, it's too damaged.
很遗憾 损坏太严重了
If you want to know where these bots are coming from,
要想知道这些机器人是在哪制作的
I'm going to have to get my hands on a live one.
得给个正常的让我来研究
So to speak.
就这样
You're quiet. What's wrong?
你很安静 怎么了?
Just looking at that bot on Rudy's table makes me think,
看着那个在Rudy桌上的机器人 我在想
who is going to remember me?
谁会记得我呢?
You're a cop.
你是名警察
The people you help will remember you,
你帮助过的那些人会记住你的
whatever your name is.
无论你叫什么名字
Speaking of names, someone just responded to your dating profile, John.
说到名字 你的交友资料有人回复了 John
My dating pro... I thought you were kidding.
我的交友资...我还以为你在开玩笑
Not kidding- I saw the way you were looking at those sexbots.
不是玩笑 我注意到 你看那些性伴侣机器人时的眼神了
Your profile name is... Dr. Richard.
你资料上的名字是Richard博士
- Dr. Richard. - Who likes quiche,
Richard博士 爱吃吃蛋饼
- long walks on the beach, smooth jazz. - You seriously did not call me Dr. Richard.
- 喜欢在沙滩上散步 听柔和爵士 - 真的 不要喊我Richard博士
- I thought you wanted to meet someone. - I meet plenty of women. I don't need your help.
- 我觉得你想约会 - 我约会的女人够多了 不需要你来帮忙
I- I ran a bio scan, and it looked like your testicles were at full capacity.
我对你的睾丸做了个生物检测 它们挺有生机的啊
You're scanning my balls?
你检测我老二?
I didn't enjoy it, I just...
不是我喜欢这样 是...
- Oh, my God, this is unbelievable. - I can't help but notice you're backed up.
- 天啊 真不可思议 - 但我就是注意到你有反应了
What is the matter with you?
你到底是怎么了?
Don't scan my testicles ever again.
以后不准再瞄我老二
Copy that.
收到
What does she look like?
她长什么样?
What do you want her to look like?
你希望她长什么样?
Brown eyes, soulful.
棕色眼睛 深情款款那种
- Height? - Average height.
- 身高呢? - 中等
I like brunettes.
我喜欢黑色头发的
Would you date anyone in your profession
你喜欢跟同行的人约会么
or would you prefer to date someone outside of it?
还是更喜欢不同行的人?
Sure, either way.
都没问题
I like smart women, you know, women that are smarter than me.
我喜欢聪明的女人 你懂的 比我还要聪明
That won't be hard.
这个也不难
You are aware that you just described
你知道自己刚刚在说的是
Detective Stahl, right?
Stahl警探的吧?
Kennex.
Kennex
Hey, we got a 20 on the silver sedan you posted. I just uploaded it to Dorian.
嘿 刚发现了你们要找的 那辆银色轿车的位置 我传给Dorian了
Uh, okay, thank you, um,
哦 好 谢了
Detective Stahl, thanks.
Stahl警探 谢谢
- Okay, thank you, Detective Stahl. - Shut up.
- 好 谢了 Stahl警探 - 闭嘴
Shut it, zip it.
闭上 封好
Police!
警察!
- Don't you move! Put your hands on the dashboard! - Hands up! Hands on the dash!
- 手举起来 放在仪表盘上 - 不许动 手放在仪表盘上!
- Do not move! - Hold 'em, keep 'em there!
- 不许动 - 抓住他们 看好了
Put your hands on the dashboard now
手放在仪表盘上 立刻
- where I can see 'em! - Turn around, turn around!
手放到我能看到的地方 转身 转身
- Step out of the car. - ???
从车里出来
Come on.
快点
Around front.
趴在前面
Hi, I'm Vanessa.
嗨 我是Vanessa
- Hey, how you doing? - I need to take a DNA sample.
- 嘿 你做什么? - 我需要提取份DNA样本
- Open your mouth, please. - Why?
- 嘴巴张开 - 为什么?
I've passed all my tests.
我所有检测都通过了啊
Please.
请张开
Her DNA belongs to a Lorraine White, abducted from a parking structure
她的DNA是属于一个 叫Lorraine White的女孩的
two months ago in St. Clair.
两个月前在St.Clair一家停车场被绑架
- Lab. - Rudy, found you some skin.
- 实验室 - Rudy 给你找到些皮肤样本
The Albanians aren't telling us where the kidnap victims are.
那些阿尔巴尼亚人不肯说出被绑者的位置
We need to get that information from a sexbot.
我们需要从性伴侣机器人那得到信息
We have three missing girls out there somewhere, maybe more.
已经有三名女孩不见了 或许不只三名
I'll pull everything I can from it.
我会尽量追查的
Hello again.
又见面了
A human's DNA was used to make your skin.
你的皮肤是用一名人类女孩的DNA做成的
This woman. We need to find her.
就是她 我们需要找到她
We don't have much time. Have you seen her before?
时间不多了 你见过她吗?
- No. - I need you to think.
- 没有 - 请再想想
It's really important.
这真的很重要
- Have you seen her? - No.
- 有见过她吗? - 没有
Where were you made?
你是在哪里被制造出来的?
Who owns you?
主人是谁?
Do you know where you were born?
你知道自己是在哪里降生的吗?
You ever worked with this girl?
有没有跟这个女孩一起工作过?
- Charlene. - Right, Charlene.
- Charlene - 对 是Charlene
Do you know where she was born?
知道她是在哪里降生的吗?
Who owns you?
你的主人是谁?
She's probably not conscious of those terms.
她可能不太明白这些词语
- Where were those men taking you tonight? - They were taking me for a ride.
- 那些人今晚要带你去哪? - 去兜风
- We think they were taking you to be destroyed. - Why would anybody want to destroy me?
- 我们认为他们要把你带去销毁 - 为什么要销毁我呢?
There are much, much better things to do with me.
有很多更好玩的事可以跟我做啊
We don't have to do anything if you don't want to.
你要是不愿意 我们可以什么都不做
I'm a very, very good listener.
我是个很好的倾听者
You know, people look for connections in different ways.
知道么 不同的人有不同的相处模式
That's all people are looking for,
但大家都在寻找的
is someone who cares about them.
不过是个关心自己的人
That's what I'm here for.
所以我才会出现在这
Do you know where Charlene is?
你知道Charlene在哪吗?
- Yes. - Can I see her?
- 嗯 - 我可以见她吗?
Why do you want to?
为什么要见她呢?
- I don't know. - You were designed to bond with people.
- 我也不知道 - 你们被设计出来就是为了与人相联结的
That's what you were developed to do.
开发你们的初衷
To notice when they're there.
是要你们在那些人在的时候注意到他们
That also means you notice when they're not there.
这也就意味着 他们不在的时候你们也会注意到
That's why you want to see her.
所以你才会想见她
That's what you're feeling.
这就是你的感受
Who told you to go with the men we found you with tonight?
谁让你跟今晚那几个男的走的?
Yuri.
Yuri
Do you know Yuri?
你们知道Yuri吗?
Yeah, we know Yuri.
嗯 知道
I'm going upstairs.
我上楼
Time to go.
该走了
Abandon everything.
所有东西都抛下
Destroy the lab.
把实验室破坏了
They'll die.
她们会死的
They can still generate so much skin.
她们还能生成那么多皮肤
We'll set up somewhere else.
我们会在别的地方建起来的
Let's go.
行动!
You go first.
你先进
- They're not here. - This isn't the right building.
- 他们不在这 - 不是这栋楼
Office is empty, too.
办公室也没人
I think I can find the skin lab.
我能找到皮肤制作实验室
- Rudy? - Yes, Dorian?
- Rudy? - 怎么了 Dorian?
Most of these sexbots are platformed on an old UJuno Pendant Learning Module.
大部分性伴侣机器人被组建时 都是基于一种老式的UJuno Pendant学习模块
Uh, yeah, uh, those modules were available to the public sector once we stopped using them on the DRNs.
对 如果DRN不使用了的话 还可以用于公共领域
Problem was that they were giving off an unwanted GPS signal.
问题是它们总是会发出一种GPS信号
Yeah, it was an unwanted side effect.
嗯 这个算是副作用吧
Um, whenever they, uh, automatically updated their software,
每当它们自动更新软件的时候
they'd inadvertently send out a signal allowing those so inclined to, uh,
就会同时发出一种信号 能让那些人追踪到
- track you. - Is there a log of that?
有相关的记录吗?
I'm sure there is.
当然有
Can you access Vanessa's internal GPS log to find the very first time that the module sent a signal?
你能进入Vanessa内置的GPS日志 找到第一次发出信号的记录吗?
- It's possible. - If we can find out
应该是有可能的
- the first time she was activated, we can find... - Find out where she was born.
- 如果能找到她第一次被激活的地点 就能找到... - 她降生的地方
The skin lab.
那间皮肤实验室
All right, bear with me.
好吧 不要介意哈
I won't be a minute. Oh. Look at that.
很快的 看这个
That's the charger for my- doesn't matter. Um, here we go.
这是我那个充电的...没啥 继续找
This is the one I need.
这个才是我要找的
right. Uh, hello.
没错 那个 你好
I need to access your data port.
我需要接入你的数据入口
That sounds rude. Um, I need to insert my... Oh, that's even worse.
有点粗鲁哈 那个 我需要插进我的... 啊 这个更粗鲁
Um... Oh, friendly.
那个 很友好的
Um, it's nothing sexual, I assure you.
跟性爱无关的 我保证
Not that there's anything wrong with sex. I mean, who doesn't like sex?
不是性爱有什么问题 我是说 哪有人不喜欢性爱啊 是吧
Not me. I mean, I do. That's-that's the point.
我可不是那类人 我是说 我喜欢性爱 这是我想表达的
But that would be, um, inappropriate at best.
但 那个 现在不大合适
This is not gonna hurt, I promise you. There we go.
不疼的 我保证 来
right. Just, um...
对 就...
having a look at your, uh...
看看你的那个...
...statistics.
数据
Looks like you
看起来
were first activated in Kingston Heights.
你第一次被激活是在Kingston Heights
Clear!
安全!
Take him out!
干掉他!
No!
不!
- Drop that weapon! - Drop it, you!
放下武器 放下武器!
- Drop the weapon! - John.
- 放下武器 - John
Don't shoot! On the ground! Now!
- 别开枪 - 立刻趴下!
Clear!
安全!
- Clear. - Clear!
- 安全 - 安全!
Clear!
安全!
- This is Lorraine White. - She's deceased.
- 是Lorraine White - 已经死了
Call Bloomquist. She's still alive.
给Bloomquist打电话 她还活着
Kristen Haseman- she's alive.
Kristen Haseman 她还活着
Victor is gonna be very happy to see you.
Victor见到你会很开心的
Great work.
干得不错
Thanks.
谢谢
- You should celebrate. - He will.
- 你该庆祝一下 - 他会的
- You have a date. - What?
- 你今晚有约会 - 什么?
- No, I don't. - Yes, you do- with the woman from the dating Web site.
- 不 我没有 - 你有的 跟婚恋交友网站上那个女的
Wha...? No.
什么? 不要
He has a wonderful profile. She's expecting you at 7:00.
他的资料很棒的 你俩7点见面哈
That's a... it's just a... it's a joke, you know.
只是...只是个玩笑 你懂的
I get a lot of women. I mean, not a lot- you know, just...
我有很多女朋友的 我是说 不是很... 你知道的 我只是...
You should celebrate no matter what.
不管怎样 你都该庆祝下
Have a great night... on your date.
约会愉快哈
- Thanks. - Good night.
- 谢谢 - 晚安
Benedict Android strikes again.
Benedict Android又乌龙了
- I can't go on a date tonight. - Why?
- 我今晚不能去约会 - 为什么?
Because I've already got someone I want to see.
因为我有想要见的人
- But, John, if you just... - Do you have your report done?
- 但John 如果你... - 报告写完了吗?
Uh, yeah, almost.
嗯 差不多完了
We'll need individual certificates when the bots are destroyed.
机器人被销毁时 需要有人在场见证
- Okay? - Okay.
- 好吧? - 好
I'm sorry. We can't have bots with human DNA.
很遗憾 机器人身上是不允许携带人类的DNA的
She has to be deactivated. But well done. Very well done.
她必须要被停止使用 但你们的表现很好 不错
- Thank you. - See you tomorrow.
- 谢谢 - 明天见
You okay?
你还好吧?
I'd like to be there.
我想去
Thank you.
谢谢
Where am I going?
我要去什么地方?
To a better place.
去更好的地方
Will you be there?
你也会去吗?
I will remember you.
我会记得你的
Marty, do you remember John Kennex?
Marty 还记得吗 是John Kennex
He was your dad's partner.
他曾经是你爸爸的搭档
I want to tell you about your father.
我想跟你说说你父亲
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入